卢比奥·德波尔，下午好，欢迎来到 CNN。
Rubio de Pol, good afternoon, welcome to CNN.
Rubio de Pol, buenas tardes, bienvenido a CNN.
下午好，非常感谢。
Good afternoon, thank you very much.
Buenas tardes, muchas gracias.
他在赛季初看起来不错，问题是他能休息多少时间？
He looks good at the start of the season and the question is how much rest has he been able to do?
se le ve bien en el arranque de temporada y la pregunta es ¿cuánto ha podido descansar?
嗯，事实是这样的
Well, the truth is that
Bueno, la verdad que
随着俱乐部比赛的数量。
with the number of games there are in the club.
con la cantidad de partidos que hay en el club.
以及关于阿根廷国家队的一切，在本例中是美洲杯，
and with everything about the Argentine National Team, in this case the Copa América,
y con todo lo de la Selección Argentina, en este caso la Copa América,
虽然只有几天，但最终我还是在做自己喜欢的事情。
It was only a few days, but well, in the end, I'm working on what I like.
Fueron pocos días, pero bueno, al final, trabajo de lo que me gusta.
我不能抱怨。
I can't complain.
No me puedo quejar.
我这样说是因为这是一场几乎在全世界（只有欧洲）不断出现的辩论。
I say this because it is a debate that is practically all over the world, only in Europe, constantly appearing.
Lo digo porque es un debate que está prácticamente en todo el mundo, solo en Europa, de forma constante apareciendo.
日历，似乎没有人可以给出解决方案。
the calendar and it doesn't seem like anyone can give it a solution.
el calendario y no parece que nadie le pueda dar solución.
你在美洲杯，赛季刚刚开始，但是马德里竞技获得了世俱杯的参赛资格，也就是说赛季能结束吗？
You were in the Copa América, the season is starting, but Atlético de Madrid is qualified for the Club World Cup, that is, can the season end?
Usted estuvo en la Copa América, está arrancando la temporada, pero es que el Atlético de Madrid está clasificado para el Mundial de Clubes, ¿es decir, la temporada puede terminar?
十个月内。
in ten months.
en diez meses.
没错，是的，嗯。
Exactly, yes, well.
Exactamente, sí, bueno.
去年有与国家队的比赛。
Last year there was competition with the national team.
El año pasado hubo competición con la selección.
今年是世俱杯，另一年是世界杯。
This year the Club World Cup, the other year the World Cup.
Este año el Mundial de Clubes, el otro año la Copa del Mundo.
看来一切顺利的话，几年都不会了。
It seems that if everything goes well, it won't for a few years.
Parece que si todo va bien, durante algunos años no.
我们不会有很多假期。
We're not going to have many vacations.
No vamos a tener muchas vacaciones.
我觉得还是要结合案例来分析。
I think it is a case to analyze.
Creo que es un caso para analizar.
生而为人，一切都有一个恢复的过程。
of being human beings and in the end everything has a recovery process.
de ser seres humanos y al final todo tiene un proceso de recuperación.
我觉得还有一点就是精神上的。
I think there is also a point where it is mental.
creo que también hay un punto en el que es mental.
这一点并没有受到太多重视。
that is not given much importance.
que no se le da mucha importancia.
我总是说我们是。
I always say we are.
Siempre digo que somos.
我们不是足球运动员，但我们是踢足球的人。
We are not soccer players, but we are people who play soccer.
No somos jugadores de fútbol, sino somos personas que juegan al fútbol.
但是，嘿，就是这样。
But hey, that's what it is.
Pero bueno, es lo que toca.
有些人...
There are people who...
Hay gente que se...
他们还必须照顾球员的健康。
who must also take care of the health of the players.
que se debe encargar de la salud también de los jugadores.
但我们别无选择，只能竞争并努力代表。
but we have nothing left but to compete and try to represent.
pero a nosotros no nos queda más que competir y tratar de representar.
就我而言，我会以最好的方式献给马德里竞技队和阿根廷队。
In my case, to Atlético de Madrid and the Argentine team in the best possible way.
en mi caso al Atlético de Madrid y a la selección argentina de la mejor manera posible.
毫无疑问，准备四四年一定很困难。
Without a doubt, it must be difficult to prepare for a siqua year.
Sin duda, debe ser complicado prepararse para un año de sicua.
当你好的时候，十二月、三月，你不可能全年都好。
When you are well, in December, in March, you cannot be well all year round.
Cuando estás bien, en diciembre, en marzo, no puedes estar bien todo el año.
没有人。
Nobody.
Nadie.
不，让我们看看，显然有更累的时候。
No, let's see, obviously there are times when one is more tired.
No, a ver, obviamente que hay momentos en los que uno está más cansado.
身体，有时是头部，但最终足球
the body, sometimes the head, but in the end football in
el cuerpo, a veces la cabeza, pero al final el fútbol en
他对此知之甚少，有人问他什么。
He understands little of that and one asks him what.
Entiende poco de eso y uno le pide en qué.
让他每三天表演一场比赛。
Let him perform every game, every three days.
que rinda cada partido, cada tres días.
这是我们必须做的事情的一部分。
It's part of what we have to do.
Es parte de lo que nos toca.
除了我们之外，没有人会按照我们的方式提出要求。
No one but us is going to demand the way we do.
Nadie más que nosotros se va a exigir de la manera en que
一个人想做这件事，但我希望事情总是顺利。
in that one wants to do it, but I hope that things always work out.
en que uno lo quiera hacer, pero ojalá que las cosas siempre salgan.
正如我们所希望的那样，尽管有时有些因素不允许。
as we want, although sometimes there are factors that do not allow it.
como queremos, aunque a veces hay factores que no lo permiten.
他说的话很有趣，因为我听他说过一次，谈论足球运动员的心理健康，
What he says is interesting, because I have heard him say it once, talking about the mental health of the footballer,
Es interesante lo que comenta, porque se lo he escuchado alguna vez, hablando de la salud mental del futbolista,
这是一个通常不会被谈论但非常重要的话题。
A topic that is generally never talked about and that is very important.
Un tema que generalmente nunca se habla y que es muy importante.
让人们认识到他的重要性当然也很重要，因为会有很多足球运动员......
Giving visibility to a person of his importance is surely important too, because there will be many footballers...
que a una persona de su importancia le dé visibilidad, seguramente lo es también, porque habrá muchos futbolistas...
他们不谈论它，但这很重要。
They don't talk about it, but it is vital.
que no hablan de eso, pero que es vital.
是的，我认为精神部分是...
Yes, I think the mental part is...
Sí, yo creo que la parte mental es...
它与身体一样重要，甚至更重要。
It is as or more important than the body.
es tan o más importante que el cuerpo.
足球运动员是一个人。
The soccer player is a human being.
El jugador de fútbol es un ser humano.
你越快乐，你的工作表现就越好，我认为在任何工作环境中都是如此。
The happier you are, the better you will function in your job, I think that is like that in any work environment.
más contento estés, mejor vas a funcionar en tu trabajo, creo que en cualquier ámbito laboral es así.
越平静，就越休息。
the calmer, the more rested.
cuanto más tranquilo, cuanto más descansado.
球员也承受着许多压力和义务。
The player also lives with many pressures and obligations.
El jugador también convive con muchas presiones, obligaciones.
在所有的工作中，我都会向你提到这一点，但是......
In all jobs there is this thing that I mention to you, but...
En todos los trabajos hay esto que te nombro, pero...
足球运动员带着一种感觉
The soccer player carries a feeling
El jugador de fútbol conlleva un sentimiento
非常普遍，有些人...
very widespread, some people...
muy generalizado, una gente...
很多时候他们的情绪取决于他们支持的俱乐部的表现。
Many times their moods depend on how the club they support is doing.
Muchas veces sus estados de ánimo dependen de cómo le vaya el club del que se hincha.
有一部分责任是你所肩负或背负的。
There is a part of a responsibility that you shoulder or are burdened with.
Hay una parte de una responsabilidad que te cargas o te cargan.
将所有这些都扛在一个头上并不容易。
It's not easy to carry all that on one head.
que no es fácil llevar todo eso por una sola cabeza.
所以，好吧，在精神方面，我认为你必须......
So, well, on the mental side I think you have to...
Entonces, bueno, en la parte mental creo que hay que...
必须高度重视，有非常有资格的人。
It must be given great importance, there are very qualified people.
Hay que darle mucha importancia, hay gente muy capacitada.
如果每个人都有足够的空间来下载或查找工具，那就太好了。
and it would be nice if everyone had that space to be able to download or find tools.
y estaría bueno que todos tengan ese espacio para poder descargarse o encontrar herramientas.
让这项工作变得不那么容易。
to make this job less easy.
para llevar este trabajo menos fácil.
在你的具体情况下，这更复杂，因为我来读......
And in your particular case, this is more complicated because I have come to read in...
Y en su caso particular, esto es más complicado porque he llegado a leer en...
好吧，首先，在美国，你被称为阿根廷贝克汉姆，你如何处理所有有关小报的报道？
Well, in America, above all, where you have been called, the Argentine Beckham, how do you handle all that about the tabloid press?
bueno, en América, sobre todo, que a usted le han llamado, el Beckham argentino, ¿cómo lleva usted todo eso de la prensa rosa?
这是另一个负担。
It's another burden.
Es otra carga.
不，不是真的。
No, not really.
No, la verdad que no.
我对此不太重视。
I don't give much importance to that.
No le doy mucha importancia a eso.
我认为这也是...的一部分
I think it's also part of...
Creo que es parte también de...
它是人们创造或发生的角色。
It is a character that people create or happen.
Es un personaje que la gente va creando o va sucediendo.
我先做我的工作，然后开始我的个人生活。
I do my work, then in my personal life.
Yo hago mi trabajo, después en mi vida personal.
我生活得很平静，这就是我可以告诉你的。
I live very calmly and that's what I can tell you.
Vivo muy tranquilo y eso es lo que te puedo decir.
最后三个。
Last three.
Tres últimas.
罗德里戈，足球界存在种族主义吗？
Rodrigo, is there racism in football?
Rodrigo, ¿hay racismo en el fútbol?
不仅在西班牙，而且在美国，也有很多讨论。
There is also a lot of talk, not only in Spain, but also in America.
Se habla muchísimo también, no solo en España, también en América.
我想，在这个世界上。
I think that in the world.
Yo creo que en el mundo.
种族主义。
racism.
el racismo.
专注于足球...
Focus on football...
Focalizarlo en el fútbol...
我相信世界上存在种族主义。
I believe that there is racism in the world.
Yo creo que en el mundo hay racismo.
我希望它不存在。
I hope it doesn't exist.
Ojalá que no exista.
但是，嘿，这也...
But hey, that too...
Pero bueno, eso también...
适合每个能够并且在镜头前的人的方式
A way for everyone who can and is in front of a camera
Una manera de que todos los que pueden y están enfrente de una cámara
他们必须有一个非常明确的信息，首先这是一个教育问题。
They would have to have a very clear message, above all it is an issue of education.
tendrían que tener un mensaje muy claro, sobre todo es un tema de educación.
我们都是平等的。
We are all equal.
Somos todos iguales.
仅此而已，但我再说一遍，我相信世界上仍然存在种族主义。
and no more than that, but I repeat, I believe that racism still exists in the world.
y no más que eso, pero te repito, creo que el racismo todavía existe en el mundo.
你是阿根廷无可争议的领袖，而在马德里竞技你却有点缺乏……你听说过吗？
You are the undisputed leader in Argentina and at Atlético de Madrid you were lacking there like a bit... Have you ever heard that?
usted es líder indiscutible en Argentina y que en Atlético de Madrid le faltaba ahí como un pelín... ¿Lo ha escuchado alguna vez eso?
你觉得怎么样？
And what do you think?
¿Y qué le parece?
那部分意见，正如我之前告诉过你的。
That part of the opinions, as I told you before.
Esa parte de las opiniones, como te decía antes.
我们生活的世界充满了意见。
In the world we live in, which is full of opinions.
en el mundo que estamos, que está lleno de opiniones.
但最终我在阿根廷队和在马德里竞技队是一样的。
but in the end I am the same in the Argentine team as I am in Atlético de Madrid.
pero al final yo soy el mismo en la selección argentina que en el Atlético de Madrid.
我很幸运能够随阿根廷赢得一切。
I was lucky to have won everything with Argentina.
Tuve la suerte de haber ganado todo con Argentina.
这最终会让你在人们的可见度上拥有更多的优势。
and that in the end gives you a little more preponderance in people's visibility.
y eso al final te da una preponderancia por ahí un poco más en la visibilidad de la gente.
但在更衣室内，它是如何运作的，...
but inside the locker room to how it worked, to...
pero dentro del vestuario a cómo funcionó, a...
我的性格和打球方式无论在哪里都是一样的。
My character and my way of playing are the same both here and there.
mi carácter y mi manera de jugar soy el mismo tanto acá como allá.
可能会在阿根廷出现一个更新的阶段，因为时间会赶上每个人。
There comes a stage, possibly in Argentina, of renewal, because time catches up with everyone.
llega una etapa, posiblemente en Argentina, de renovación, porque el tiempo alcanza a todo el mundo.
我想，只要他愿意，就可以说玛丽亚、梅西。
Say María, Messi, whenever he wants, I guess.
Di María, Messi, cuando él quiera, supongo.
你准备好加入团队了吗？
Are you ready in the team?
¿Están preparados en el equipo?
你们在阿根廷谈论到必然会发生代际变革吗？
Do you talk about it among you in Argentina to necessarily see a generational change?
¿Lo hablan entre ustedes en Argentina a que viera obligatoriamente un cambio generacional?
让我们看看，这就像在说，时间对于每个人来说都在流逝。
Let's see, it's like saying, time passes for everyone.
A ver, es como decir, el tiempo pasa para todos.
每个人都知道我与里奥、信仰联盟、迪玛利亚的亲密关系。
Everyone knows about my closeness with Leo, with Fide, with Di María.
Todos saben de mi cercanía con Leo, con Fide, con Di María.
它们是我们的常规对话，对吧？
And they are regular conversations that we have, right?
Y son charlas habituales que tenemos, ¿no?
我特别认为...
I particularly think that...
Particularmente pienso que...
哈哈哈
hahaha
jejeje
当他们不在场时，准备工作是非常困难的，因为他们就是这样的球员。
In preparing for when they are not there it is very difficult because they are such players.
en la prepararse para cuando no estén es muy difícil porque son jugadores tan
其规模如此之大、如此之主导，以至于无法取代它们。
so large and so predominant that it is impossible to replace them.
tan grandes y tan preponderantes que es imposible sustituirlos.
我认为作为一个团队，有更多关于工作计划的讨论。
I think that there is more talk about a work plan as a group.
Yo creo que ahí se habla más de un plan de trabajo como grupo.
使其尽可能不引人注目。
make it noticeable as little as possible.
que se note lo menos posible.
但是，我还特别与您谈论退休的安赫尔的案例，以及，利奥，我希望......
But well, I'm also talking to you particularly about the case of Ángel, who retired, and well, Leo, I hope that...
Pero bueno, también te hablo particularmente del caso de Ángel, que se retiró, y bueno, Leo, espero que...
愿他还剩很多年，一次又一次地回来
May he have many years left now he came back again and again
que le queden muchos años ahora volvió y otra vez
他打进了两个球，是一名37岁的球员。
he scored two goals, a 37-year-old player later.
hizo dos goles, un jugador de 37 años después.
由于脚踝问题，自美洲杯以来他就没有参加过比赛。
that he had not played since the Copa América due to an ankle problem.
de que no jugaba desde la Copa América por un problema en el tobillo.
回来后仍然与其他人有很大不同。
comes back and is still very different from the rest.
vuelve y sigue siendo muy diferente al resto.
所以我希望我们能享受更多年，这对我来说是一种荣幸。
So I hope we can enjoy it for many more years and that is a pleasure for me.
Así que ojalá lo podamos disfrutar un montón de años más y para mí es un placer eso.
看来世界杯要来了。
It looks like the World Cup is coming.
Tiene pinta que el Mundial va a llegar.
希望不是真的。
Hopefully, not really.
Ojalá, la verdad que no.
我认为他还不知道。
I don't think he even knows it yet.
Creo que ni él todavía lo sabe.
取决于你的体质感觉如何。
depending on how your physique is feeling.
dependiendo de cómo su físico se vaya sintiendo.
但显然对我们来说，希望如此。
But obviously for us, hopefully.
Pero obviamente que para nosotros, ojalá.
希望如此，因为我已经告诉过你，不仅在球场上，而且......
Hopefully, because I already told you, not only on the field, but...
Ojalá, porque ya te digo, no solo dentro de la cancha, sino...
外在是非常非常重要的。
outside is very, very important.
fuera es muy, muy importante.
冠军联赛开始。
The Champions League begins.
Arranca la Champions.
新的冠军联赛。
The new Champions League.
La Champions nueva.
你怎么认为？
What do you think?
¿Qué le parece?
好吧，事实是我还没有……
Well, the truth is that I don't have one yet...
Bueno, la verdad que no tengo todavía una...
对新冠军的看法非常成型，因为最终它没有开始。
A very formed opinion of the new Champions because in the end it did not start.
Una opinión muy formada de la nueva Champions porque al final no comenzó.
我们必须看看它如何发展。
We would have to see how it develops.
Habría que ver cómo se va desarrollando.
去年之前我们看到的欧冠联赛非常精彩。
The Champions League that we saw until last year was spectacular.
La Champions que vimos hasta el año pasado era espectacular.
他们仍然是世界上最好的球队。
They are still the best teams in the world.
No dejan de ser los mejores equipos del mundo.
世界上最好的球员，最好的球队。
the best players in the world, the best teams.
los mejores jugadores del mundo, los mejores planteles.
我认为这将是一场精彩的演出。
I think it's going to be a great show.
Creo que va a ser un gran espectáculo.
我希望周四我们能顺利起步。
I hope that on Thursday we start on the right foot.
Ojalá que nosotros el jueves arranquemos con el pie derecho.
马里竞技队的六名阿根廷人。
Six Argentines at Atlético de Marí.
Seis argentinos en el Atlético de Marí.
作为教练消费。
Consuming as a coach.
Consumiendo de entrenador.
这是好是坏？
Is that good or bad?
¿Eso es bueno o malo?
没什么好说的。
Nothing good.
Nada bueno.
好吧，事实是我们有好几个人。
Well, the truth is that there are several of us.
Bueno, la verdad que somos varios.
这是一群非常好的伙伴。
It is a very nice group of mate.
Es un muy lindo grupo de mate.
好吧...
And well...
Y bueno...
归根结底，足球界最美丽的地方就是更衣室。
In the end in football the most beautiful thing is the locker room.
Al final en el fútbol lo más lindo es el vestuario.
这是训练课程，因为比赛日到了，你必须赢球，压力很大。
It's the training sessions, because then match day arrives and you have to win and there is a lot of pressure.
Son los entrenamientos, porque después llega el día de partido y hay que ganar y hay mucha presión.
许多义务和专注，但仅此而已
many obligations and concentrations and nothing of all that
muchas obligaciones y las concentraciones y nada todo eso
当你离开时，你会想念阿根廷，现在我们成立了一个小团体，我们在其中做一些事情......
When you are away you missed Argentina and now a little group was formed in which we do things that...
Cuando estás lejos lo extrañabas de Argentina y ahora se armó un grupito en el que hacemos cosas que...
这些在我们国家很常见，比如打牌、喝马黛茶。
that are very common in our country, like playing cards, drinking mate.
que son muy cotidianas desde nuestro país, como jugar a las cartas, tomar mate.
一些烧烤，同样的音乐，坎比亚。
some barbecue, the same music, the cumbia.
algún asado, la misma música, la cumbia.
我很享受它。
I'm enjoying it a lot.
Yo lo estoy disfrutando un montón.
回到朱利安·阿尔瓦雷斯的例子，你对他的到来感到惊讶吗？
Returning to the case of Julián Álvarez, were you surprised that he arrived?
Volviendo en el caso de Julián Álvarez, ¿le ha sorprendido que haya llegado?
来了对你有什么帮助吗？
Has coming helped you in any way?
¿Ha ayudado usted en alguna medida que haya venido?
在我们发送的一些小消息中...
In some little messages we send...
En algunos mensajitos mandamos...
但我认为...
but I think...
pero creo que...
他还谈到了朱利安，关于......
He also talks about Julián, about...
Habla también de Julián, de...
个性和...
of personality and...
de la personalidad y de...
饥饿感，挑战自我的欲望。
of hunger, of the desire to challenge oneself.
del hambre, de las ganas de desafiarse.
你认为朱利安是一个23岁的人吗？
Do you think Julian is a 23-year-old person?
¿Vos pensáis que Julian es una persona de 23 años?
谁赢得了一切。
who has won everything.
que ha ganado todo.
欧洲冠军联赛、解放者杯、美洲杯、世界杯。
The Champions League, the Copa Libertadores, the Copa América, the World Cup.
La Champions, la Copa Libertadores, la Copa América, la Copa del Mundo.
在他踢球的地方，他赢得了一切。
Where he played he won everything.
donde jugó gano todo.
不顺从，那就是想要突破极限。
and does not conform, that is wanting to push the limits.
y no se conforma, eso es querer empujar los límites.
明白总会有更多。
understanding that there is always a little more.
entendiendo que siempre hay un poco más.
所以，他接受的这个挑战……
So, this challenge that he takes...
Entonces, este desafío que él toma...
这并不容易，因为马德里竞技队的期望非常高，这对于他这样的球员来说很正常。
and it is not easy because Atlético de Madrid's expectations, which is normal for a player of his quality, are very high.
y que no es fácil porque las expectativas del Atlético de Madrid, que es normal a un jugador de su calidad, son muy grandes.
而不是这里的这个。
and instead of this here.
y en cambio de esto de por aquí.
在曼彻斯特找到了一个宁静的地方，并且知道他们拥有一支伟大的球队。
having found a place in Manchester of tranquility and knowing that they have a great team.
haber encontrado un lugar en Manchester de tranquilidad y de saber que tienen un gran equipo.
他总是想要更多，所以我认为他在谈论
He always wants a little more, so I think he's talking about
él quiere siempre un poco más, entonces creo que habla de
他是谁，他的心态，他的饥饿感，好吧，我们，至少是我，喜欢......
of who he is, of his mentality, of his hunger and well, we, at least I, like...
de quién es él, de su mentalidad, de su hambre y bueno, nosotros, por lo menos yo, como...
作为一个更大的球员，作为一个队友，我会努力陪他去实现
also as a bigger player and also as a teammate, I will try to accompany him to achieve
también como más grande y como compañero también de selección voy a intentar acompañarlo a que logre
他来寻找的就是头衔。
what he came to look for, which are titles.
lo que vino a buscar, que son títulos.
另一件肯定会逃脱的事情，我想知道你的意见，是马竞今年有......
Another thing that will surely have escaped, I would like to know your opinion, is that Atlético this year has a...
Otra cosa que seguramente habrá huido, me gustaría saber su opinión, es aquello de que el Atlético este año tiene una...
非常非常好的球队，拥有非常重要的签约，他们必须要求他们与马林和巴萨一起战斗一切。
very very good squad with very important signings and they have to demand that they be there fighting with Marín and Barça everything.
plantilla muy muy buena con fichajes muy importantes y que tiene que exigirse estar ahí peleando con el Marín y el Barça todo.
你内心怎么想？
What do you think inside?
¿Qué se piensa de dentro?
当一个人成为一名足球运动员时
The one that when one becomes a soccer player
El que ya cuando uno se convierte en jugador de fútbol
如果一个人对自己的要求...
If the demand that one has for oneself...
Si la exigencia que tiene uno mismo...
外面的人不可能给你。
It is impossible for someone from outside to give it to you.
Es imposible que alguien de afuera se lo dé.
除了我们自己，我们如何要求自己？
More than ourselves, how do we demand ourselves?
Más que nosotros mismos, ¿cómo nos exigimos?
它并不存在，但这也导致我们走到了现在的位置，并为我们竞争的东西而竞争。
It does not exist and that also led us to be where it is and to compete for the things we compete for.
no existe y eso también nos llevó a estar donde está y a competir por las cosas que competimos.
我认为我们有一支很棒的球队。
I think we have a great squad.
creo que tenemos un gran plantel.
我认为我们在皇家马德里和巴塞罗那的联赛中竞争......
I think we compete in a league in which Real Madrid and Barcelona...
Creo que competimos en una liga en la que el Real Madrid y Barcelona...
他们也有获胜的义务，但对我来说......
They also have that obligation to win, but to me...
tienen también esa obligación de ganar, pero a mí...
作为一个愿望和梦想，我很高兴能够在马德里竞技队获得冠军。
As a wish and as a dream, I would love to be able to achieve a title with Atlético de Madrid.
Como deseo y como sueño me encantaría poder lograr un título con el Atlético de Madrid.
最终一队获胜，仿佛有三四支队伍有着相同的目标……
In the end one wins, so as if there are three or four teams that have the same objective...
Al final gana uno, entonces como que si hay tres o cuatro equipos que tienen el mismo objetivo...
不是每个人都会遵守。
Not everyone will comply.
no todos lo van a cumplir.
在内部，目标非常明确，但在消息中我们了解到......
Internally, the objective is very clear, but in the message we understand that...
Internamente sí que el objetivo está muy claro, pero en el mensaje entendemos que...
还有两支非常强大的球队，这将是一场并不容易的战斗。
that there are also two teams that are very strong and that it is going to be a battle that is not easy.
que hay dos equipos también que son muy fuertes y que va a ser una batalla que no es fácil.
谁拒绝了独立的提议。
who rejected an independent offer.
que rechazó una oferta independiente.
故事是这样的，当我还是个孩子的时候
The story is that when I was a boy
La historia es que cuando yo era chico
当我很小的时候，他们就来独立队接我。
They came to pick me up from Independiente when I was very little.
A mí me vinieron a buscar de Independiente cuando era muy pequeño.
到我玩过的邻居，然后...
to my neighborhood where I played and...
a mi barrio donde yo jugaba y...
我告诉妈妈我不会去那个俱乐部。
I told my mom that I wasn't going to that club.
Le dije a mi mamá que a ese club no iba.
因为我支持前面的一项，那就是赛车。
because I root for the one in front, which is Racing.
porque yo hincho por el que está enfrente, que es Racing.
维罗纳是一个小轶事，它仍然是独立的。
Verona is a small anecdote, it is still independent.
Verona es una pequeña anécdota, no deja de ser independiente.
一个伟大的俱乐部，一切都充满尊重。
A great club and always everything with a lot of respect.
Un grandísimo club y siempre todo con mucho respeto.
他在欧洲的时光，他在瓦伦西亚的首秀，非常奇怪。
His time in Europe, his debut in Valencia, was very strange.
Muy raro su paso por Europa, su debut en el Valencia.
如果它持续得很好，它也会持续，因为
it lasts also if it lasts nice because
dura además si dura linda porque
今天看到这个观点，让我成长了很多。
Today, seeing this perspective, it made me grow a lot.
Hoy, viendo lo de esta perspectiva, me hizo crecer mucho.
这对我们来说并不容易。
It's not easy for us.
No es fácil para nosotros.
17、18岁时，远离家乡，最终你皈依了。
At the age of 17, 18, going so far from your home, in the end you convert.
A la edad de 17, 18 años, irte tan lejos de tu casa, al final te convertís.
首先是作为一名专业人士，然后是作为一个成年人。
first as a professional, before as an adult.
primero en profesional, antes que en adulto.
拥有这一切并与这一切战斗并不容易
and it is not easy to have all that and fight with all that
y no es fácil tener todo eso y luchar con todo eso
但我对我的时光有着美好的回忆，因为现在它是那些
but I have a great memory of my time because now it has been one of those that
pero me queda un gran recuerdo de mi paso porque ahora ha sido uno de los que
在我成长最快的地方，因为最终一个人会随着打击而成长。
in the places where I grew the most, because in the end one grows with the blows.
en los lugares que más crecí, porque al final uno crece con los golpes.
更衣室里谁最搞笑？
Who is the funniest in the locker room?
¿Quién es el más gracioso del vestuario?
你和谁笑得最多？
Who did you laugh with the most?
¿Con quién se reía más?
我认为我和安托万在更衣室里擦出了火花。
I think that between Antoine and I we put the spark in the locker room.
Yo creo que entre Antoine y yo le ponemos ahí la chispa al vestuario.
事实上，我们有非常相似的幽默感。
The truth is that we have a very similar sense of humor.
La verdad que tenemos un sentido del humor bastante similar.
所以我认为它就在那里。
So I think it goes there.
Así que creo que va por ahí.
大家，我认为我们是一群非常有趣的人。
Everyone, I think we're a pretty funny bunch.
Todos, creo que somos un grupo bastante gracioso.
巴西队在世界杯预选赛中发生的事情对你来说是不是很奇怪？
Does what is happening with Brazil in the World Cup qualification seem strange to you?
¿Le parece extraño lo que está pasando con Brasil en la clasificación para el Mundial?
巴西就是巴西，而且……
Brazil is Brazil and...
Brasil es Brasil y...
我认为他将获得参加下一届世界杯的资格，并且将成为最受欢迎的球员之一。
I think he was going to qualify for the next World Cup and will be one of the favorites.
Yo creo que se iba a clasificar a la próxima Copa del Mundo y será uno de los favoritos.
为了它的历史，为了它的球衣，为了它拥有的球员。
for its history, for its shirt, for the players it has.
por su historia, por su camiseta, por los jugadores que tiene.
这是所有团队都经历的过渡时刻。
It is in a moment of transition in which all the teams go through it.
está en un momento de transición en el que todas las selecciones lo pasan.
我告诉你，它之所以能引起共鸣，是因为它是巴西。
I'm telling you, it's resonant because it's Brazil.
Ya te digo, es resonante porque es Brasil.
我相信他们最终会参加下一届世界杯，凭借他们拥有的球员，他们将成为热门球队之一
I believe that in the end they will play in the next World Cup and with the players they have they will be one of the favorites
Yo creo que al final van a jugar la próxima Copa del Mundo y con los jugadores que tienen será uno de los favoritos
今年你会高兴什么？
What would you be happy with this year?
¿Con qué estaría contento este año?
如果这个赛季发生什么事情，你会说今年非常好？
What would have to happen in the season for you to say that this year has been very good?
¿Qué tendría que pasar en la temporada para que usted dijera que este año ha sido muy bueno?
大家都知道，我不考虑个人的事情。
Those who all know, I don't think about the personal.
Los que todos saben, yo no pienso en lo personal.
我的愿望和最大的梦想是为马德里竞技队赢得冠军。
My wish and my biggest dream is to win a title with Atlético de Madrid.
Mi deseo y mi sueño más grande es ganar un título con el Atlético de Madrid.
我们将竭尽全力来实现这一目标。
and we will give everything we have to achieve it.
y nos dejaremos todo lo que tenemos para lograrlo.
尽管有时不可能，但我认为可以尝试。
and although sometimes it is not possible, I think it is possible to try.
y aunque a veces no es posible, intentarlo creo que es.
也莫名其妙地成功了，总是再试一次。
also somehow succeed, always try again.
también de alguna manera triunfar, siempre volver a intentarlo.
人们对团队的方式感到认同...
that people feel identified with how the team...
que la gente se siente identificada a cómo el equipo...
开发...
Develop the...
Desarrolla lo...
马德里竞技队历史上最重要的几分，正在战斗到最后。
the most important points in the history of Atlético de Madrid, which is fighting until the end.
los puntos más importantes que tiene la historia del Atlético de Madrid, que es el luchar hasta el final.
比永不放弃。
than never give up.
que nunca darse por vencido.
因此，就这一切以及我们的阵容而言，
So, in relation to all that and with the squad we have,
Entonces, en relación a todo eso y con el plantel que tenemos,
我希望能达到某种程度，尽管我知道这并不容易。
I hope it is with some degree, although I understand that it is not easy at all.
Ojalá que sea con algún título, aunque entiendo que no es para nada fácil.
好吧，我要说的是保罗，非常感谢你接受 CNN 采访，祝你好运，希望他能成功。
Well, I say this about Paul, thank you very much for being on CNN, good luck and let's hope he can make it.
Pues lo digo de Paul, muchas gracias por estar en CNN, muchísima suerte y esperemos que pueda conseguirlo.